arclook.com 2016-01-21

# Privacy Policy | Arclook.com

### arclook.com does not collect or share personal information

Privacy is a hot topic these days, and we want you to feel totally comfortable using our service, so our privacy policy is very simple: when you search with arclook.com, we do not collect any personally identifiable information, period. We have no idea who sends queries: not by name, not by IP address, and not by cookies.

**Logs:**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement, and gather broad information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Email:**

If you chose to opt-in to receive promotional or information email from arclook.com, we will occasionally send advertisements, marketing material or other offers on behalf of other businesses that we think might be of interest to you. This material is sent by arclook.com, and we do not give the other businesses your email address. If you do not want to receive these advertisements, marketing material or other offers, please opt out of these communications by clicking the unsubscribe link provided in each email.

**Future Business Transfers:**

In the event arclook.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or prominent notice in our website before 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

**Disclosure:**

We may disclose your personally identifiable information not limited to email address, if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority. We will not sell your personally identifiable information not limited to email address to any other company or organization except we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which arclook.com participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of arclook's assets. Such successor entity shall be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

**Cookies:**

arclook.com uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use arclook.com services in order to improve the quality of our services. 

**Other Sites:**

arclook.com role is to redirect you to other websites / content providers that you are searching for. We do not control those sites even if you are redirected to them via arclook.com. We are not responsible for any of their actions and privacy policy.

**Correction/Updating/Deleting Personally Identifiable Information:**

arclook.com provides you with the ability to review, correct and delete any of the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us. If you wish to review, correct or delete any information you have provided to us, you may contact us at [support@arclook.com](mailto:support@arclook.com). 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement page, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on our homepage. Questions or Concerns if you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at arclook.com, please send us a detailed message to [support@arclook.com](mailto:support@arclook.com).  
You may also write to us:  

Dev Soft Technologies Inc.762 Green St. Suite 2E Iselin NJ 08830

We will make every effort to resolve your concerns. Effective date: Oct 15, 2013
